Jörg Bernhard Reske

Tel.: (+5584) 99968-5830 Email: jorg.reske@gmail.com

Project Manager | UX/UI Designer | App Developer

As a versatile developer and creative designer, I am passionate about crafting impeccable digital art, ranging from web pages and logos to billboards and various business documents. My approach involves adapting to diverse client needs, offering comprehensive digital solutions with agility, and expertly addressing challenges by identifying, isolating, and resolving any difficulty. With a keen sense of empathy, I understand client requirements and consistently strive to exceed customer expectations. My strong dedication to companies is complemented by effective leadership skills, fostering collaboration across different areas.

Career Achievements and Accomplishments

Welcome to my portfolio! I'm Jörg Bernhard, a seasoned professional with over 12 years of experience transitioning into a UX/UI Designer. Throughout my career, I've successfully created over 100 web pages, company logos, banners, and project documents. In the latter part of my professional journey,

I took on the role of a Project Manager for over 8 years, overseeing the completion of 210MW wind power projects and registering over 10,800MW for development throughout Brazil. Notable projects include conducting a cell tower analysis for AT&T in the United States and spearheading a warehousing project for Garoto with 10,750 pallets in South America.

Employment History

General Manager | 2009 - 2022

Acera General Consulting, Marketing Development for company sale. Integrated Agile Methodologies to enhance the flow of information and data within the companies.

IT Manager, Pacific Hydro for South America | 2007 - 2009

Provided IT services such as networking and construction of a long-range network for wind farms..

General Manager, Siah | 2002 - 2007

IT and Marketing Manager, developed the marketing area, and created a sales structure. Project development for Desbravador.

General Manager, Hotel Rosa Náutica | 2001 - 2007

Oversaw hotel management, customer service, and marketing.

IT and Marketing Manager, TTI | 1998 - 2001

Led marketing projects and implemented ISO 9002.

Project Manager, AT&T, USA | 1997 - 1998

Contributed to the development of a cellular project for AT&T in Maricopa Desert, Arizona, USA.

Design Manager | 1993 - 1997

Coordinated project activities.

Education:

University of Köln: Administration;

Humboldt Technical School International:

Trade Management;

PCD: Web Design; Spanish (basic)

Cubos Academy: Fullstack Developer

Coursera: UX/UI Design.

Languages:

German • native English • professional Portuguese • professional Spanish • basic